revostock.com 2015-06-09

# RevoStock -Privacy Policy

**REVOSTOCK.COM PRIVACY POLICY**

Personal information for purposes of this policy is defined as information that identifies You, individually, including but not limited to Your name, home address, home telephone number, and e-mail address.

We only collect personally identifiable information about You after You have specifically provided such information to Us.  By voluntarily submitting this information to Us when using our Website, You are consenting to the collection and use of Your personal information by Us for that online activity.  You are under no obligation to provide Us with this information and You can access many parts of the Website without providing Us any personal information. 

If You participate in an online activity which requires You to provide personal information, such information will only be used for the purposes of that online activity, unless You consent otherwise.  By way of example and not limitation, We may collect and use personal information for some or all of the following reasons:

�         Responding to questions or comments forwarded to Us by You.

�         To operate chatrooms, bulletin boards or other areas of interaction with other users.

�         Selection and notification of contest winners.

�         To collect data on use of the Website.

�         To provide You with notices that may be required under contracts You enter with Us.

�         To communicate with You regarding billing, payment and other issues related to any business You conduct with Us.

�         To provide You with notice of upcoming promotions.

This Privacy Policy applies only to Us.  Please be aware that the Website may contain hyperlinks to other websites.  We have no control over any such Websites and are not responsible in any way for information that is provided to them.

Remember that when You voluntarily disclose information on the bulletin boards or in the forum or chat areas of our Website, all information disclosed in Your communication becomes public information and can be collected and used by other parties.  You acknowledge that We cannot control what third parties in the bulletin board or chat areas do with Your personal information.

**DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES**

We will not sell or rent Your personal information to any other party without Your consent.  However, We may use or disclose Your personal information without Your consent for the following reasons:

1.   Your name and city may be published by Us or one of Our sponsors if You have entered and won one of Our contests.  Please check the specific contest rules for details.

2.   In emergency situations or when required by subpoena or governmental authorities.

3.   In connection with an organizational change in Our company, merger or acquisition, or the sale of all or substantially all of Our assets, provided that the information disclosed continues to be used for the purposes allowed by this Privacy Policy.

**SECURITY**

RevoStock has extensive security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information stored in our database. These measures include the use of Secure Server technology during credit card transactions and administrative access to site data, as well as other security measures. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure. 

**NON PERSONAL INFORMATION**

In addition, We collect non-personally identifiable information, which is information that does not identify You personally, but becomes available to Us as a result of Your use of the Website.  This information includes: Your IP address, a number automatically assigned to Your computer when You visit the Website, Your internet service provider and Your web browser.

This non-personal information is used as a tool for identifying system problems and administering the Website.  From time to time We use "cookies" on this Website.  "Cookies" are small text files that Your web browser leaves on Your hard drive to recognize You as a repeat user of Our Website.  If You do not want "cookies" to be used, You may disable them by accessing the features of Your web browser.

We collect personal and non-personal information in a non-identifying, anonymous and aggregate form to enhance Our Website, to share with advertisers and for statistical purposes.  These statistics and reports will contain only aggregated and no personally identifiable information.

**RE-MARKETING WITH GOOGLE ANALYTICS**

RevoStock uses analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website.  Site visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google advertising opt-out page") or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout "Google Analytics opt-out page").

Google has additional information available about their [Remarketing Privacy Guidelines](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746 "Google's Remarketing Privacy Guidelines"), [Policies](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=143465 "Google's Remarketing Policies"), and [Restrictions](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=178363 "Google's Remarketing Privacy Restrictions").

**AMENDMENT TO PRIVACY POLICY**

This policy is subject to change.   We reserve the right, at Our discretion, to revise this Privacy Policy at any time, and such revision shall be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised version at the Website. You agree to review these Privacy Policy periodically to become aware of such revisions. If any such revision is unacceptable to You, You may cease using the Services and terminate Your account. Your continued use of the Services following posting of a revised Privacy Policy on the Website shall be deemed to be acceptance of the revisions.
